We can blame it all on the weather
Zenbu tenki no sei de ii yo
All this awkwardness and exhaustion
Kono kimazusa mo kentaikan mo
The sun hides away, pretending not to see
Taiyou wa kakure nagara shiranpuri
A packed train clatters along the track
Gatagoto yureru manin densha
It brushes past a local express
Surechigau no wa junkyuu ressha
I'm gonna search for feelings in a shapeless cloud
Rinkaku no nai kumo no hyoujou wo sagashite miru
The test asks, "How was the author feeling here?"
“Sakusha no kimochi wo kotaenasai”
What could the right answer possibly be?
Ittai nani ga seikai nan dai?
Breaking through the script of pre-established harmony
Yotei chouwa no shinario fuminuite
Everyone talks about the "springtime of life"
Aoi haru nante mon wa
And I'm just not cut out for that
Boku ni wa niawanain da
Yet I know that this moment,
Sore demo shitteru kara
which will never come again,
Ichido shika nai shunkan wa
is rich with evanescence
Hakanasa wo haranderu
I will never forget, ever
Zettai wasurete yaranai yo
So many times before I die someday...
Itsuka shinu made nankai datte
I'll laugh thinking about what it was like
Konna koto mo attatte waratte yan no sa
I feel like the wind's leaving me behind
kaze ni oite karesou de
So I'm desperately clinging on
Hisshi ni kuraitsuiteru
That familiar sound of the bell
Itsumo no kane no ne mo
That dust piled up on the window sill
Madogiwa ni tsunda hokori mo
Even the smell of the classroom
Kyoushitsu no nioi datte
I will never forget, ever
Zettai wasurete yaranai yo
So many times before I die someday...
Itsuka shinu made nankai datte
I'll laugh thinking about what it was like
Konna koto mo attatte waratte yan no sa