BOCCHI THE ROCK!
#08 Bocchi the Rock
What's wrong with not letting my sound die down?
What's wrong with being young?
BOCCHI THE ROCK!
#08 Bocchi the Rock
Hey, why doesn't it stop?
The rhythm that I can't stop
keeps reverberating through my body
The melody playing in my earphones
is the only thing that lets me be who I am
The sky is tinged in red
But what color is my soul?
Tell me
where should I go?
I've always been searching
for something precious (hey!)
If everything's going to be lost some day
let's engrave it as deep as we can (now!)
My most pathetic nights and cackling laughter
And days when I couldn't say more than "You know..."
(I'm alive now, yeah Springtime of life)
What's wrong with not letting my sound die down?
What's wrong with being young?