The tune that plays when my loneliness
and the pedal are stepped on
Tracks down my cheeks over and over again
The pounding of my loneliness
Is joined by the rhythm of the snare drum
To create a solid pulse
Someone, please remove the distortion on my heart
And take a look inside me
Nobody can get inside my heart
But it's the kind of night
when I hope someone will
Distortion, it's motion
Once it starts, there's no stopping it
Limits can be overwritten with experience
Isn't that right?
Distortion is always like that
My heart takes off, outpacing my left brain
Toward where you are
An escort to the next note
Distortion on my day-to-day anguish
The chord I play when I'm alone at night
Is it the same for you?
I spent all those days chasing my ideal image
Play an F chord with distortion
So loud that the needle swings off the scale