I liked dark, cramped spaces,
so I'd bury my face deep in my hood
My eyes resented the heartless world,
but yearned for love
I liked being soaked by the rain,
because my face looked better clouded over
I pretended to be afraid of the storm
while waiting for the sky to burst
Strum through the light's distortion
I want to make thunder roar
beyond
the
pain
beyond
the
pain
Drum
beyond
the
pain
Drum
beyond
the
pain
Drum
beyond
the
pain
Drum
beyond
the
pain
What can I do?
This fierce pounding is out of control
Strum in a harmonizing quartet
I want to cause a revolution
Drum in a lamenting forte
What can I do?
My savage nature is beyond wild