That band's songs sound to me
ano bando no uta ga watashi ni wa
like shrill laughter all around
Kandakaku hibiku waraigoe ni kikoeru
That band's songs are to me
Ano bando no uta ga watashi ni wa
like the piercing clang of a railway crossing
Tsunzaku fumikiri no oto mitai
Don't push me forward
Senaka wo osu na yo
There's a train coming
Mou soko ni ressha ga kuru
I close my eyes
Me wo tojiru
There's a halo in the darkness
Kurayami ni sasu gokou
I cover my ears
Mimi fusagu
There's a steady beating pulse within
Tashika ni kizamu kodou
Deep in my chest
Mune no oku
My heart makes my body sway
Mi wo yurasu shinzou
I don't want to hear anything else
Hoka ni nanmo kikitakunai
Nothing but the sounds I'm making
Watashi ga hanatsu oto igai